aoi hoshi ni senritsu ga hashiru
a
o
i
ho
shi
ni
se
n
ri
tsu
ga
ha
shi
ru
A shudder runs over the blue planet
푸른 지구에 전율이 흐른다
kuroi arashi chikazuku toki
ku
ro
i
a
ra
shi
chi
ka
zu
ku
to
ki
It's the time the dark storm approaches
검은 폭풍이 닥쳐오는 순간
kokoro no oku de mezameru HERO
ko
ro
no
o
ku
de
me
za
ru
HE
RO
It's as if a hero is awakening on the inside
마음 속의 눈을 뜬 영웅들이여
tobitatsu no da furimukazu ni
to
bi
ta
tsu
no
da
fu
ri
mu
ka
zu
ni
Fly away and don't look back!
뒤돌아보지 말고 날아가라
DAGWON kagayake DAGWON
DA
G
WON
ka
ga
ya
ke
DA
G
WON
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
Brave Command Dagwon
용자지령
다그온
Dagwon... Shine on!! Dagwon!
다그온 빛나라!! 다그온
heiwa mamoru namae sa
he
i
wa
ma
mo
ru
na
ma
e
sa
The name that protects the peace
평화를 지키는 이름이다
DAGWON oretachi DAGWON
DA
G
WON
o
re
ta
chi
DA
G
WON
Dagwon! We are Dagwon!
다그온 우리는 다그온
yume wa zettai watasanai
yu
me
wa
ze
t
ta
i
wa
ta
sa
na
i
We will never hand over our dream
꿈은 절대로 넘겨줄 수 없다
afureru yuuki te ni shitai nara
a
fu
re
ru
yu
u
ki
te
ni
shi
ta
i
na
ra
To grab the overflowing courage
넘쳐흐르는 용기를 거머쥐고 싶다면
tsuyoku tsuyoku yuujou shinjiru koto sa
tsu
yo
ku
tsu
yo
ku
yu
u
jo
shi
n
ji
ru
ko
to
sa
We believe in our friendship firmly
우리 우정을 굳게 믿는 거다
kizutsuku koto mo osore wa shinai
ki
zu
tsu
ku
ko
to
mo
o
so
re
wa
shi
na
i
We are not afraid of getting hurt
상처입는 것도 두렵지 않아
mugendai no mirai wo egaku sono tame ni
mu
ge
n
da
i
no
mi
ra
i
wo
e
ga
ku
so
no
ta
me
ni
In order to reach that infinite future!
무한대의 미래를 그려내기 위해서라면
This is...
이건...
A long time ago, there was an unknown phenomenon.
옛날부터 세계 각지에서 일어나고 있는
Kamigakushi: Children randomly missing, believed to be done by an evil spirit
that appears in every corner of the world, called Kamigakushi.
수수께끼의 현상, 행방불명
However, its cause is still unknown.
하지만 그 원인은 아직까지도 규명되지 않았습니다
Maria's Ghost Extermination
마리아의 유령퇴치
Space Ghost Ship Vander Seijin
Appears
우주 유령선 반다 성인
등장
Kamigakushi....
행방불명인가...
My Supernatural Phenomenon Research Club is not properly formed yet
우리 초상현상 연구회도 발족 의뢰는 아직이고
and there's no real outcome of study at the moment.
이렇다할 연구 성과는 전혀 없으니까 말야
This is bad.
곤란한걸, 이래선...
What a frightful fog...
안개 한번 짙게 꼈네
Shit!
마, 맙소사...
Gaku, what are you doing?
가, 가쿠! 뭐하고 있는거야?!
Look out!
위험하잖아!
Hey, Gaku, wait!
가쿠도 참, 얘!
No!
위험해!
Ouch...
아이구, 아파라...
You're heavy, Maria...
무거워, 누나...
Gaku, what are you doing sleepwalking?
가쿠! 너 자다가 뭘 하는거야?
Walking on the fence is dangerous!
담장 위에서 걸어다니다니, 위험하잖아!
Look at this.
이거야, 이거
I'm asking you what this is about!
그니까, 그게 뭐냐구
You don't know?
모르겠어?
Many children have disappeared.
수많은 아이들이 사라져 버렸어
This is the modern Kamigakushi.
이거야말로 현대의 행방불명이야
There you go again, you occult girl.
또 시작했군, 오컬트 소녀
En Daidouji, from now on, you're appointed as a temporary member of the Supernatural Phenomenon Research Club.
다이도우지 엔, 지금부터 당신을 초상현상 연구회의 임시 부원으로 임명합니다
What?! Why do I have to be a member of such an uncanny club?!
뭐야? 내가 도깨비 클럽의 임시부원이라고?!
You're wrong!
아니야!
A temporary staff of Supernatural Phenomenon Research Club.
초상현상 연구회의 임시부원이야
What about temporary staff?! It's stupid!
뭐가 임시부원이냐?! 바보같구만!
To call it a group, it's a super minor club where you're the only member!
애시당초 연구회라고 해봤자 부원은 꼴랑 너 하나밖에 없는 초 마이너한 동호회잖아!
Who'll fall over that?
누가 그딴데에...
How can you say such things to your friend?
친구에게 그런 식으로 말하다니...
How cruel!
너무해!
I'm not that stupid to fall over that trick!
그런 속임수에 내가 넘어갈 거라고 생각하냐?
And ever since I born,
게다가, 머리털 나고서 여태껏
I never considered you as a friend!
너를 친구라고 생각해본 적은 한번도 없어!
Give it back.
돌려줘
The 5000 yen you borrowed from me a while ago.
얼마전에 빌려간 5000엔
Give me back all of it right now.
지금 당장 한푼도 빠짐없이 돌려줘
Th-that's... too much...
그, 그런...
M-M-Maria dear,
마, 마, 마리아 쨩~
Aren't we friends?
우리, 친구 아니니...
Give it back!
돌려줘!
I'm counting on you! Do me a favor!
부탁이야! 이렇게 빌게!
It's a wish of my life!
일생의 소원이야!
Please lend me 5000 yen!
5000엔만 빌려주라, 응?
5000 yen!
5000엔!
Why do we have to pay you back the money you borrowed from her?
어째서 저희들이 엔이 꾼 돈을 갚아야 합니까?
Not worth considering.
말도 안되는 소리지
Please don't say that!
그런말 하지 말고 말야
We're a team, right?
우리는 한 팀이잖아?
Hmph! Are we a team only when you need us?
흥! 니 꼴릴 때만 팀 꺼내냐?
Without 5000 yen, I will be in big trouble!
5000엔 없으면 난 큰일난단 말야
Please...
제발...
Very well.
알았습니다
Re- really?!
저, 정말?!
Yay! That's what I would expect from my friend!
앗싸! 역시 넌 내 친구야!
But first, give me back 2000 yen you borrowed from me.
하지만 그전에, 요전에 꿔간 2000엔을 갚으세요
2-2000 yen?
2, 2000엔?
Just as I thought.
역시 잊고 있었군요
Did I borrow?
언제 꿨었나?
Hey! Stop!
에잇! 기다려라!
A high school student is not supposed to be in debt!
건전해야할 고등학생이, 빚이 웬말이냐?!
I'll fix your completely rotten nature!
네놈의 썩어빠진 근성을 바로잡아주마!
It was a mistake! I shouldn't asked for help from this guy!
실수다! 이녀석에게 부탁한게 실수였어!
But still I have Ryu, who I can always count on!
역시 이런 때에 믿음직한건 류 군밖에 없구나
Hey! Ryu! Where are you?
어~이, 류 군~ 어딨니~?
Ryu?
류~ 군~?
Here I am.
여기다
Ryu! My friend!
류 군! 나의 벗이여!
I couldn't eat anything from yesterday.
어, 어제부터 아무것도 못 먹었어
Wouldn't you lend me money?
돈 좀 빌려주지 않을래?
I'm counting on you, En.
부탁이다, 엔...
What do I do now?
이거 글렀구만...
I'm ready!
이걸로 준비 끝~!
Let's go investigate the Kamigakushi full of mystery!
수수께끼의 행방불명 조사 출발!
I'm not going! Absolutely not!
난 싫어! 절대 안할거라구!
What are you talking about?
무슨 소리니?
This is also for the discovery of unknown world.
이것도 미지의 세계의 해명을 위한 거라구
But why do I have to be a bait?
그렇다고 해서 왜 내가 미끼가 돼야 하는건데?!
It's alright! The expert of Supernatural Phenomenon Research Club, I, Tobe Maria, is behind you.
괜찮아! 네 뒤에는 이 초상현상 연구회의 토베 마리아가
So you just keep close to me!
빈틈없이 붙어 있으니까 말야
That's why I don't want to go.
그래서 싫다는 거라구
It'll be fine, follow me.
됐으니까 따라와
Pity me.
한심하구만
Let's go back and go sleep!
이제 그만 돌아가서 자자
Shh. Keep quiet.
쉿, 조용히 해
Hmph! Do as you want.
쳇! 혼자 멋대로 하라구
Sheesh...
정말...
Cut...
바람을...
the wind!
가른다!
Is it a fog?
안개인가?
What are you doing?!
무슨 짓이야?!
Lo- look.
저, 저길 봐
It's just like how it was yesterday.
어제와 똑같아
What exactly is this?
어떻게 된거냐, 저건?
This must be the modern Kamigakushi!
역시 이건 현대의 행방불명?
It can't be!
말도안돼!
Let's follow them!
추척 개시하자
Cut...
바람을...
the wind!
가른다!
This should be enough for tonight.
오늘밤은 이정도로 해 둘까
Is that En and Maria?
저건 엔과 마리아?
A juvenile boy and girl wandering around together in a deep night...
이런 한밤중에 미성년 남녀가...
Unforgivable!
용서 못한다!
Damn! Where are they going to?!
젠장! 어디까지 가는 거냐?!
H-hey, look at that.
자, 잠깐 저거...
W-what is this?!
뭐, 뭐야 이건?!
W-wait a moment!
자, 잠깐 기다려!
This is bad!
큰일이구만
Hey! What are you doing?!
잠깐! 무슨 짓이야?!
Why did you let the rope go?!
왜 줄을 놓은거야?!
Hurry and go grab it!
얼른 붙잡아 와!
Don't say something stupid!
바보같은 소리 하지마!
I'm not doing such unpleasant things!
그런 기분 나쁜 짓을 할 수 있을 것 같냐?!
Then what will you do?
그럼 어쩔거야?!
We lost Gaku!
가쿠가 있는 곳을 알 수 없게 되어 버렸잖아!
W-what's that?!
뭐, 뭐지 저건?!
A g-ghost ship!
유, 유령선...!
No way!
말도 안돼!
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
용자지령
다그온
Original Korean Subtitles by Jaebari (재바리)
Translated to English by Subdivers
Checked by Great Exkaiser103
자막 원본(번역): 재바리
수정: Subdivers
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
용자지령
다그온
The children must be trapped...
아이들은.. 저 배에게...
in that ship... There's no doubt about it.
끌려간게... 틀림없어...
What's that?
뭐냐, 저건...
That can't be a real ghost ship.
설마 진짜 유령선은 아니겠지?
What are you doing? Help me!
뭘 멍하게 서있는 거야? 좀 도와줘!
What are you doing?
너야말로 뭘 하고 있냐?!
Isn't it obvious?
당연하잖아!
We're going to get into that ship with this boat.
이 보트로 저 배에 타는거야
Are you an idiot?!
바보냐, 너?!
Please, I won't say anything bad!
험한 소리 안할테니까, 응?
Nope! We came here to do this!
싫어! 애써 여기까지 왔는걸
We're not going to do this ever again!
이런 체험, 다시는 할 수 없어
So hurry up and help!
어서 도와줘!
I should've known this from the start.
애초에 같이 오는게 아니었어..
En!
엔!
What are you doing? Hurry and come.
뭘 하고 있나? 어서 타라
A-as expected, Kai...
위, 위험한 전개;;;
Kai!
카이~!
That's our chair of discipline! Good timing!
과연 풍기위원장! 굿 타이밍!
We can't stand watching children's crisis.
아이들의 위기를 잠자코 보고 있을 순 없다
Let's go, En.
가자, 엔
The world hates me...
최악이구만....
Hurry and row faster!
좀 더 빨리 저으라구
Shut up!
시끄러!
Why do I have to row the boat all by myself?!
대체 어째서 나 혼자 노를 저어야 되는거냐구?!
Shh. Silence.
쉿, 조용히 해라
I don't like this place.
왠지 기분 나쁜걸
There's no doubt. This ship came from the secondary dimension.
당연하지, 이 배는 이차원 공간
Or, from the world of spirits.
다시말해 영계에서 온거야
The children must be inside somewhere this ship!
이 배의 어딘가에 아이들이 있을 거야
Let's go!
가자!
Wind.
바람이다
The wi- wind, huh?
바, 바람이구나
I can't see anything in this darkness!
정말, 어두워서 아무것도 안보이는구만
What are you so scared about?
뭘 그리 쫄고 그러니?
Shut up! Don't try to jump out of nowhere!
시끄러! 갑자기 튀어나오지 마!
Gale Strike!
열풍참!
What was that for? Just a cockroach.
뭐야, 바퀴벌레잖아
Let's go.
가자
She got rid of cockroach with a bare hand...
바퀴벌레를 맨손으로...
What's the problem, Kai?
왜그래, 카이?
Cockroach...
바, 바퀴.. 바퀴...
This way! This way!
이쪽이야, 이쪽
That can't be the ghost...
설마, 지금 그게 유령의 정체는 아니겠지?
Of course not.
그럴 리 없잖아
Let's go!
가자!
I can't open it!
안열려!
What?
뭐라고?
This time it isn't wind!
이번엔 바람이 아니야!
No way! Is this a supernatural phenomenon as well?
말도 안돼! 이런 심령현상도 있어?!
The enemy is probably trying to kill us.
아무래도 적은 우리를 죽이려는 것 같군
Why the heck are you so calm?!
침착하게 있을 때냐?!
Foul Trick Sword!
역수검! (역주 : 逆手劍 -날이 자기쪽을 향하게 쥠)
I'm done with this.
이제 싫어...
Kai! What was that for?!
카이! 갑자기 무슨 짓이야?!
Look!
봐라!
Those are...
이건?!
...the lost children.
행방불명이 됐던 아이들이야
Gaku!
가쿠!
Maria!
마리아!
Don't you think this ghost uses a way too advanced weapon?
호오, 유령 치고는 꽤 진보한 무기를 쓰는군
Earthlings...
지구인이여
Good work on coming here.
잘도 여기까지 왔구나
So Kamigakushi was an alien after all?!
행방불명의 정체는 우주인이었단 말인가?!
Why did you kidnap the children of Earth?
무슨 목적으로 지구의 아이들을 유괴하지?
The children of earthlings are worth a lot!
지구인의 아이들은 이용 가치가 높다
Try Dagwon!
트라이 다그온!
Fire En!
파이어 엔!
Try Dagwon!
트라이 다그온!
Turbo Kai!
터보 카이!
You bastards are Dagwon!
너희들은, 다그온?!
Heh? We're famous among them!
헤에? 우리도 꽤 유명한데?
Shin! Yoku! Come here right now!
신! 요쿠! 이쪽으로 와줘!
You'll be melted thoroughly.
걸쭉하게 녹여주마
You bastard!
이자식!
I see!
그렇군!
Stop that!
그만둬!
Just as I suspected!
역시 그랬어!
This ship itself is an alien!
이 배 자체가 우주인이다!
I see! That's it!
과연, 그랬던 거구만
Why you-!
이자식!
Damn!
제길!
-You're not getting away!
-Yeah! Let's combine!
-안 놓친다!
-오우! 합체다!
Merging Fusion!
융합합체(融合合體)!
Dag Fire!
다그 파이어!
Merging Fusion!
융합합체(融合合體)!
Dag Turbo!
다그 터보!
Are both of you all right?
두사람 모두 무사해?!
Shadow Jet!
섀도우 제트!
Stop! There are kidnapped children inside!
그만둬! 저 안에는 유괴당한 아이들이 있어!
What? Children are?
뭐야? 아이들이?!
I see. Everything's now clear!
과연, 그랬던 거구만
What should we do? We can't let it run away!
어쩔 겁니까? 그대로 두면 놓쳐 버립니다!
Nothing's going to stop us now! Let's finish it up with Lio Sword!
이판사판, 라이오 소드로 작살내 버릴까?
No way! That's too dangerous!
말도 안돼! 너무 위험해!
Then what should we do?
그럼 어떻게 해야 되지?!
That's...
저건?!
I did it! Got out successfully!
성공이다! 탈출 성공!
That occult girl's doing something wild again!
저 오컬트 소녀! 터무니 없는 짓을 하는구만!
Great. Children should be with Maria!
좋았어, 마리아와 함께 아이들도 있을 터다
Maria, great!
마리아, 장하다!
Dag Fire, cut where Maria is using Lio Sword.
다그 파이어, 라이오 소드로 마리아가 있는 곳을 잘라줘
Alright, understood!
좋아, 알았어!
Blazing Fusion!
화염합체(火炎合體)!
Fire Dagwon!
파이어 다그온!
Lio Sword!
라이오 소드!
Eat this! Kidnapper alien!
받아라! 유괴 우주인!
We're falling!
떨어진다~!
Children are all safe.
아이들은 모두 무사해
The final blow!
끝이다!
Liner Tackle!
라이너 태클!
Thank you, Fire Dagwon!
고마워, 파이어 다그온!
You saved us! Thank you so much!
덕분에 살았어 정말 고마워
See ya!
그럼, 안녕!
He's so cool! Bye-bye, Fire Dagwon!
멋지다! 바이바이~ 파이어 다그온~
By the way, where did those two go?
그러고보니, 그 두사람은 어떻게 됐지?
Hey!
어~이!
Maria, what a relief!
마리아, 다행이다
Oh, I see you guys are safe.
어머? 무사했구나, 너희들
What's with that attitude?!
뭐, 뭐야 그 말투는?
-We were busy...
-Stop it.
-우리는 말야!
-그만둬
How can you run away in an important moment?
나 참, 중요한 때에 어디론가 가 버리고 말야
You guys really are useless in a fight!
너희들은 정말 도움이 안되는구나
Hey! We were just...
이봐! 우리는 너를...
Stop it, En. Don't face her.
그만둬, 엔 상대하지 마라
Kai, you too.
카이도 마찬가지야
You were swinging a wooden sword with force
잘난듯이 죽도 휘두르더니만
and a single cockroach scares you?
겨우 바퀴벌레 한마리에게 쫄고 말야
So much for chair of discipline.
정말 못미더운 풍기위원장이라니까
So, everyone, let's go home.
자, 얘들아 집으로 돌아가자
Kai. Aren't you angry after that?
카이... 그런 소리 듣고도 안 열받냐?
En, I give you permission to show her.
엔, 인정하마 혼내줘라
Alright!
좋았어!
Go away!
싫어~!
Gale Strike!
열풍참!
The sun suddenly called me
태양이 갑작스레 나를 불러내서
taiyou ga fui ni ore wo izanau
To come to the blue sea
푸르게 비치는 바다로 만나러 갔지
aoku sukitooru umi ni ai ni kita
The ripples are coming and going
밀려왔다 돌아가는 잔물결
yosete wa kaesu sazanami
An endless melody
멈추지 않는 멜로디
tomaru koto nai MELODY
sono sugata towa ni tsunagu you ni
To keep that shape for eternity
그 모습을 영원히 유지할 수 있도록
I'll follow the fate of the dream
꿈의 행방을 뒤쫓아 갈 거야
oikakete yuku yo yume no yukue
Sparkling far away
멀리서 반짝이던
tooku kirameita
kaze no naka no PRISM
A Prism in the Wind
바람 속의 프리즘
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
Preview for Next Episode
용자지령
다그온
차회예고
En, where's Geki Kuroiwa?
엔, 쿠로이와 게키는 어딨지?
That guy went somewhere with Maria.
그녀석이라면 마리아를 데리고 어딘가로 가 버렸어
-Weird guy.
-Did Geki do something?
-취미 한번 별나군
-게키가 뭔 짓이라도 했어?
-Brave Seijin has appeared again.
-Then it might be...
-브레이브 성인이 또 나타났다
-에엣, 그거 혹시...
Right. I think there is a new member to Dagwon.
그래, 우리 다그온에게 새로운 멤버가 생긴 것 같아
Who's that? What kind of guy is he?
누구냐, 어떤 녀석이지?
-Don't you know?
-No.
-너, 모르냐?
-몰라
You're one slow guy!
무서울 정도로 둔한 녀석!
Next time on Yuusha Shirei Dagwon! Dagwon No. 6
다음회 용자지령 다그온 다그온 No.6
The discipline of Dagwon's going to be distracted by this!
이로써 또 다그온의 풍기가 흐트러지겠군!
Dagwon No. 6
다그온 No.6